https://jeff-hough.squarespace.com/privacy

Menu
Privacy Protecting your privacy is important to us. We hope the following statement will help you understand how The Redwood Store collects, uses and safeguards the personal information you provide to us.What information do we collect?We collect information when you submit a question via our Contact page or when you contact us via phone to place an order or request information that will be delivered electronically or physically.What do we use your information for?to improve our customer service or answer your questionto process transactions - your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, traded, given, or otherwise transferred to any other company or party for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.to send periodic emails - the email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to our order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.Note:  If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.How do we protect your information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal nformation.Do we use cookies?We do not use cookies.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, exchange, trade, give, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.  We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our or other rights, property, or safety.Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.This policy was last modified on 06/01/2013.Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact use using the via our contact page.
Blog  /  Latest Article
